Guide to the Stribling, Wells and Gay Records 1817-1939 MS 599
New-York Historical Society
Stribling, Wells and Gay records
1817-1939
New-York Historical Society
MS 599
20 Linear feet in 40 boxes
TBD
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
Arrangement
TBD
Biographical / Historical
TBD
Immediate Source of Acquisition
TBD
Related Materials
TBD
Scope and Contents
TBD
Business records.; Financial records.
- Bills, accounts, correspondence, 1820-1871 (Box 1)
- No label, 1830-1899 (Box 2)
- Leases, J. Wells receipts, Ogden real estate docs correspondence, medical records (French), 1830-1900 (Box 3)
- Accounts, leases, and checks, 1817-1909 (Box 4)
- Leases, checks, receipts, 1828-1894 (Box 5)
- Accounts, correspondence, checks, 1825-1894 (Box 6)
- Correspondence, leases, church pew deeds, indentures, receipts, 1871-1900 (Box 7)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes many blank church pew deeds for Clement C. Moore at St. Peter's Episcopal Church in Manhattan.
- Leases, mortgages, accounts, correspondence, 1851-1896 (Box 8)
- Receipts, checks, James Wells rental agreements and leases, 1839-1898 (Box 9)
- Correspondence, receipts, checks, 1866-1917 (Box 10)
- Receipts, tax papers, indentures, 1866-1907 (Box 11)
- Leases, correspondence, receipts, indentures, 1864-1889 (Box 12)
- Checks, legal documents, correspondence, rental agreements, receipts, 1844-1901 (Box 13)
- Correspondence, tax papers, receipts, checks, accounts, 1858-1900 (Box 14)
- Tax papers, receipts, correspondence, 1859-1908 (Box 15)
- G.H. Ogden estate papers, contracts, leases, tax papers, 1858-1939 (Box 16)
- Leases, correspondence, accounts, 1862-1898 (Box 17)
- Indentures, tax papers, receipts, checks, 1861-1900 (Box 18)
- Contracts, correspondence, leases, 1862-1899 (Box 19)
- Leases, checks, receipts, 1833-1885 (Box 20)
- Correspondence, accounts, checks, 1845-1876 (Box 21)
- Receipts, correspondence, insurance policies, bonds, mortgages, tax papers, 1835-1878 (Box 22)
- Correspondence, contracts, receipts, checks, rental agreements, 1826-1885 (Box 23)
- Correspondence, bills, receipts, rental agreements, insurance orders, 1873-1932 (Box 24)
- Indentures, leases, correspondence, bills, rental agreements, 1844-1907 (Box 25)
- Accounts, notes, bills, leases, Clement C. Moore will, rental agreements, insurance orders, maps, 1858-1940 (Box 26)
- Bills, correspondence, rental agreements, leases, 1846-1908 (Box 27)
- Checks, 1835-1900 (Box 28)
- Bills, correspondence, rental agreements, checks, wills, tax papers, 1836-1906 (Box 29)
- Metal box, embossing tool, pencils (Box 30)
- Leases, accounts (Box 89)
- Indentures, blank contracts, German papers (receipts?), rental agreements, 1875-1927 (Box 90)
- Newspapers, indentures (Box 91)
- Embossing tools, 1927 Manhattan land book, 1927-1934 (Box 92)
- Maps, bound book (Box 93)
- Embossing tools, other artifacts (Box 94)
- Account books (Box 95)
- Account books, 1837-1939 (Box 96)
- Day books, receipt books, correspondence file, 1860-1889 (Box 97)
- Newspapers, blank NYC tax forms (Box 98)